<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Splinters on BAKAOH</title>
    <link>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Splinters on BAKAOH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 09:39:36 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bakaoh.com/splinter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Spinterlands like an Idle Game</title>
      <link>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/play-spinterlands-like-an-idle-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 09:39:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/play-spinterlands-like-an-idle-game/</guid>
      <description>What is Idle games? Idle games, or &amp;ldquo;games that play themselves&amp;rdquo;, are games which are all about management of revenue streams. The core idea of these games is that progress can be made without a player&amp;rsquo;s constant involvement. Player mainly focus on growth decisions.
These games are dominating many of the popular flash portals and shooting up the charts on mobile.
You earn in-game currency and buy upgrades. After that, you can put the game away and just check it once in a while; your purchased upgrades will earn money for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions for low level bots in tournament</title>
      <link>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/solutions-for-bots-in-tournament/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 09:39:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/solutions-for-bots-in-tournament/</guid>
      <description>Players don&amp;rsquo;t like bots because they register as many accounts as possible in the off chance that they might end up getting a prize in high level tournament just by pure luck.
Splinterlands team tried to fix that problem by adding an entry fee in an update 2 months ago. But it seems ineffective. In fact, the solution even has a negative impact. Less real players willing to pay that fee giving the bots more chance to get prizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord of Fire celebrate - an ORB give away</title>
      <link>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/lord-of-fire-celebrate-an-orb-give-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 09:39:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/lord-of-fire-celebrate-an-orb-give-away/</guid>
      <description>Today i opened some Orbs i collected from daily and season rewards. And this is what i got
And then&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s definitely Lord of Fire day.
I&amp;rsquo;m really happy with that so i will share my luck by giving away an Orb to one of you who comment below. I wish the receiver will open an Lord of Fire as well ^_^</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diamond league for the first time</title>
      <link>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/diamond-league-for-the-first-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 09:39:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bakaoh.com/splinter/diamond-league-for-the-first-time/</guid>
      <description>I started playing splinterlands 3 months ago and slowly built up my deck. With mostly silver cards, i seldom reach Gold I.
After 3 seasons trying to reach Diamond using my own deck without success, I decided to create a new account, go to https://peakmonsters.com/ and rent a Gold deck to play the last 2 days of the previous season.
This deck costs me around $20 for 30-60 days, i can use them next 2-4 seasons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>